Charge
Next, about Misora Naomi, isn't it about time that we open up the investigation to the public?
次に、南空ナオミの件ですが
もう公開捜査に踏み切るべきでは？
Next, about Misora Naomi, isn't it about time that we open up the investigation to the public?
If we do, we should try to avoid any connections being made to the Kira case.
やるならキラ事件とは無関係とし、
Use an artist's impression rather than a photo.
写真は避け似顔絵にするべきでしょうね…
But, it's already been four months since she vanished.
しかし、行方不明になってもう四ヶ月、
I can only imagine that she's dead.
すでに死んでいるとしか…
もし死んでいるとしても遺体が出てこないのはおかしい…
Even if she's dead, it's strange that no one has been able to locate her body yet.
出てくればそこから何か掴めるかもしれません
If we can find it, it may shed some light on this situation.
Ryuuzaki.
竜崎
Sakura TV.
さくらテレビを…大変なことに
Something terrible is occurring.
Basically, we're presenting this broadcast as Kira's hostages, but also as reporters fulfilling their duties.
つまり私たちは、キラの人質であると共に、
報道人の使命としてこの報道をするものであり、
Please understand that we would never air this broadcast with an intent to deceive or with a wish to gain popularity.
決して嘘や興味本位で、
このテープを放映するものではないと言う事をご理解ください
Kira's hostages?
キラの人質？
What's going on?
なんだこれは
Four days ago, the director on duty received these four tapes.
四日前、当番組ディレクターに送られてきた四本のテープ、
Without a doubt, they have been sent by Kira.
それは間違いなくキラから送られてきた物でした
Our ratings will rise by 60%... no, 70% at least!
視聴率六十パー…
いや七十パーはいくぞこりゃ
The first tape contained predictions of the date and times of death for two suspects that were recently apprehended.
一本目のテープには、
先日逮捕された二人の容疑者の、死亡時刻が予告されていました
Yesterday both suspects died at exactly their predicted times of death.
そして昨日、
二人の容疑者がその予告通り、心臓麻痺で亡くなったのです
If that is really true, it's definitely something only Kira can do.
それが本当なら、確かにキラでなければできないことだ…
We've received orders from Kira to play this second tape today at exactly 5:59pm.
そしてキラは、今日の午後五時五十九分ちょうどから
この二本目のビデオを放映する様を指示しています
We've been informed that this will contain a predicted murder as further proof that they are Kira, and also a message to the people of the world.
自分が本物のキラであると証明する予告殺人、
そして世界の人々に向けてのメッセージが入ってるとの事です
A-Are you sure that this isn't another joke?
ま、またやらせじゃないのか？
Surely... no one would pull a prank that's this sick.
まさか、いくらなんでもこんな悪質なやらせは…
Here it is.
ではご覧下さい
I am Kira.
私はキラです
If this video is being broadcast at exactly 5:59pm on the 18th of April, it should now be 5:59pm and 47... 48... 49...
このビデオが、四月十八日、
午後五時五十九分ちょうどに流されれば
今は五時五十九分、四十七、四十八、四十九…
If this video is being broadcast at exactly 5:59pm on the 18th of April, it should now be 5:59pm and 47... 48... 49...
Please change the channel to Taiyou TV now.
チャンネルを太陽テレビに替えてください
The main newsreader, Hibima Kazuhiko, will die of a heart attack at exactly 6 o'clock.
メインキャスターの日々間数彦氏が、
六時ちょうどに心臓麻痺で死にます
The main newsreader, Hibima Kazuhiko, will die of a heart attack at exactly 6 o'clock.
おい
Change it.
替えて
No way...
まさか
You okay?!
撮るな
Stop filming!
撮るな撮るな
I said turn it off!
Get help!!
撮るな
How dare they...
なんて事…
Change the channel back.
チャンネルを戻して
Hibima Kazuhiko continued to air his claims that Kira is evil.
日々間氏は、キラを悪だと主張し、報道し続けてきました
Also, bring me another TV. No, make that two.
それからテレビをここへもう一台、いや二台
はい
This is his due.
Yes.
その報いです
Another sacrifice will have to be made.
もう一人犠牲になってもらいます
The target will be someone currently live on NHN TV.
ターゲットは… NHN テレビに生出演やっている、
A commentator who's been negative about me, Kobaizumi Seiji.
私を否定してきたコメンデイター、熊泉清次氏
Ryuuzaki!
竜崎！
Turn to channel 24.
チャンネル24に！
Huh?! Pull yourself together!
Please change it back.
戻してください
I think that, by now, you should all believe that I am Kira.
これで私がキラだと言うことは信じて頂けたと思います
Kira said that they wanted to send a message to the world, but...
キラが世界の人々に向けメッセージを流すと言っていたな…
We've got to stop this broadcast, or there will be trouble!
この放送、止めさせないとまずい事になる！
I'll phone Sakura TV!
さくらテレビへ電話を！
No good, my acquaintance at the station has his phone switched off.
駄目だ、局内の知り合いの携帯は電源が入っていない
No matter what part of the station I ring it's all busy!
局のどこに掛けても通話中…
Screw this...
くそっ…
Ukita-san!
宇生田さん！
I'll go to the station in person and make them stop!
俺が直接局に行って、止めさせてやる！
Everyone, listen carefully, I don't want to kill innocent people.
皆さんよく聞いてください
私は罪のない人を殺したくありません
I hate evil, and love justice.
悪を憎み、正義を愛します
I even regard the police as my ally, and not as my enemy.
警察も私の敵ではなく、味方だと考えています
Damn you, Kira...
キラめ…
My wish is to create a world without any evil.
私の願いは、悪のない世界をつくる事です
If you all decide similarly, it should be easy to achieve.
皆さんがその気になれば、簡単にできる事です
If you cease your attempts to capture me, no innocent people will die.
私を捕まえようとしなければ、罪の無い人間は死にません
Damn...
くそ…
私に同意できなくとも、
Even if you don't agree with me, as long as you don't go to the media, or express it publicly, I won't kill you.
メディアに乗せ、公(おおやけ)にしたりしなければ、
殺したりはしません
Please try and wait a while; this world will become something that anyone would appreciate.
そして少し間、待ってください
誰もが認める世界になります
私はこの汚れた世界を…心の優しい人間を主とした
I will change this filthy world into a world that's build for gentle people.
新しい世界に変えてみせます
Try to imagine this.
想像してください、
The police and I will creat--
世界の警察と私がつくる…
Sachiko...
幸子
Darling, this is bad for your health. Please try to get some rest.
あなた、体に障ります
休んでください
Darling, this is bad for your health. Please try to get some rest.
Sachiko... I'm the Chief of the Kira Special Investigation Unit.
幸子…私はキラ事件の捜査本部長だ…
Shit! It's shut!
くそっ…閉まってる…
警察だ！開けろ！
Police! Open up!
Idiots!!
馬鹿野郎～！
We interrupt this program to bring you live footage from outside the Sakura TV station!
もしもし…
突然です、番組を変更し、
Hello? Damn it! I can't get through.
くそ、繋がらない
さくらテレビ前からの生中継を送りします
Aizawa-san!
あ…相沢さん！
As you can see, someone has collapsed!
ご覧下さい！
誰かが倒れています
This is the scene occuring outside Sakura TV right now!
これは、今のさくらテレビ前の影像です
う…宇生田さん…
Ukita-san...
く…くそ…キラか！
S-Shit!! Was it Kira?!
相沢さん
Aizawa-san!
Where do you think you're going?
どこへ行く気ですか？
To Ukita, of course.
宇生田のところに決まってるだろ
You can't.
駄目です
Please compose yourself.
冷静になって下さい
Are you telling me to just shut up and watch TV?!
ここで黙ってテレビを見てろって言うのか!!
If this is Kira's work, and you go there, the same thing will happen to you.
これがキラの仕業なら、あそこに行けば同じ目に遭います
If Kira doesn't have a name, they shouldn't be able to kill!
キラは名前がわからなければ殺せないはずだ！
So why has this happened?!
なのに何故あんなことに…！
Were the fake IDs useless?
偽名の警察手帳も無駄だった…
Maybe... Kira already knew our names?
まさか、我々の名前は、既にキラにバレているのでは？
That's a possibility.
あるいはそうかもしれません
But if Kira did know that, it would have been a lot easier for them to kill us first.
しかしそれならキラは、
捜査する人間を全員殺してから動くほうが楽なはず
But if Kira did know that, it would have been a lot easier for them to kill us first.
私の推理では、顔と名前が必要でしたが、
According to my theory, Kira needs a name and a face, but having watched this,
これを見ている限り、
顔だけでも殺せる可能性も、ゼロではないとしか…
According to my theory, Kira needs a name and a face, but having watched this,
it seems that the probability of Kira being able to kill someone solely by knowing their face, isn't zero.
Right now, the only think that I can say, is that Kira is inside the station, or at least somewhere where they can monitor the people entering--
今言えるのは、キラはあのテレビ局内…
もしくは局に入る者を監視できる所にいるということです…
If you think that Kira is around that area, there's even more of a reason to go!
キラがあの周辺にいると思うなら、尚更行くべきじゃないのか！
There's always the possibility that they set up surveillance cameras.
監視カメラを設置しているだけと言うこともありえます
If you carelessly rush out there now, you'll only be killed.
今のこのこ出て行けば、殺されるだけです
You! I thought that you were risking your life to catch Kira!
あんただって、キラの逮捕に命懸けてんだろ！
命を懸ける事と、
命をやすやす奪われる可能性のある事をするのは正反対の事です
Risking your life, and allowing someone to easily take it, are two completely different things.
Risking your life, and allowing someone to easily take it are two completely different things.
What?!
なにぃー!?
Try and hold back.
堪えてください…
Now that Ukita-san has been killed, if you were to lose your life too...
宇生田さんがやられ、
これでもし相沢さんの命まで奪われてしまったら…
Now that Ukita-san has been killed, if you were to lose your life too...
To the police; please decide whether you will cooperate with me in creating a new world, and announce your answer of "yes" or "no" in four days' time,
警察が私と協力し、
新しい世界をつくっていく事に YES か NO か…
during the 6 o'clock news on the 22nd of April.
四日後の、午後六時のニュースで発表してください
I have prepared videos for both "yes" and "no" responses.
YES の場合と NO の場合に流す、異なるビデオを用意してあります
ああっ！
What the hell is going on?!
なんなんだよ一体！
Hey! What do you think you're playing at?!
おい、どういうつもりだ！
Where's the studio that's airing the Kira tapes?!
キラのビデオを流してるスタジオはどこだ
It's a patrol van! A patrol van has charged into Sakura TV!
突入です！
さくらテレビに車が突入しました！
That's one way of entering the station without revealing your identity...
あれなら姿を見られず局内に入れます
But who is it?
しかし、一体誰が…
Police! Stop the broadcast!
警察だ！番組を中止しろ！
な…何だ
W-What's going on?
I'm telling you to stop the Kira tapes!
すぐにキラのテープを止めるんだ！
W-Wait a second Detective. If we stop this tape, we'll be killed by Kira...
ちょ…ちょっと待ってくださいよ刑事さん
これやめちゃうと私達、キラに殺されちゃうんですから…
W-Wait a second Detective. If we stop this tape, we'll be killed by Kira...
出せ！
Hand them over!
If you do that, you can save your life right now, if nothing else.
出せば少なくとも今死ぬことは免れるぞ！
W-What are you thinking?! Are you insane?
な…何考えてんだあんた
正気か…
キラをスターか何かの様に報道してきた結果だ
This is the result of you covering the Kira case as though they are some kind of star.
"You reap what you sow", don't you agree?
自業自得だと思わないか！
I want all the copies as well.
コピーしたテープも全部出すんだ
Don't even think about trying to get out of this now!
今更悪あがきをするな！
O-Okay! I'll get them, I'll get them, so stop waving that pistol around!
わぁ…わかったよ
出す出す、だから拳銃を振り回すのはやめてくれ…
Your eyes are crazy...
あんた、目がいっちゃってるよ
あ、今やっと一台のパトカーが、
Finally, a single police car has arrived outside Sakura TV.
さくらテレビ前に到着しました
So we're not the only ones... there are still others in the force that want to stand up and fight!
我々だけじゃない…
まだ警察の中にも立ち上がる者は居るんだ
So we're not the only ones... there are still others in the force that want to stand up and fight!
Aizawa-san, you know the cell phone number of Deputy Chief Kitamura, right?
相沢さん、
北村次長の携帯番号を知ってましたよね
Aizawa, I thought that I told you not to call me.
相沢、私には電話するなと…
L です、
This is L. I'd like to ask a favor of you.
北村次長にお願いがあります
この報道を見て、自己の正義感で動く警察関係者が出てきます
Upon seeing this broadcast, people connected with the police will act, driven by their own sense of personal justice.
上に統制を執って頂かないと惨事になりかねません
I'd like you to control this directly from the top, or this could turn into a disaster.
But on this case, we're...
いや…しかし私達はこの事件には…
ああ…！駆けつけた警官二人が倒れました…
Both of the policemen that rushed to the scene have collapsed!
W-We will also be evacuating the area!
わ…私達もここから避難します
わかった、 L
Understood. L, please advise me on how I should command.
どう指揮を執るべきか、アドバイスをくれ
夜神局長からです
It's Chief Yagami.
折り返しかけて電話を私に
Call him back, and hand me the phone.
Please hurry and let me talk to Ryuuzaki.
至急、竜崎を頼む
It's me. Yagami-san, so it was you in the patrol van.
私です
夜神さん、やはりあなたが護送車で
It's me. Yagami-san, so it was you in the patrol van.
Yes... I couldn't stop myself.
そうだ…
我慢できなかった…
Yes... I couldn't stop myself.
テープは全て押収した、そっちへ持っていく
I've seized all the tapes, and I'll bring them over to you.
体のほうは大丈夫なんですか
Are you alright?
大丈夫どころか、こんな元気な自分は生まれて初めてだ
I feel more than alright. In fact, I've never felt this alive before!
Never mind that, what should I do?
そのことより、どうすればいい？
I think the front entrace is dangerous, but I should be fine in the car.
正面は危険だと思うが、
あの車なら大丈夫だろうか…
ちょっと待ってください
Please wait a minute.
Deputy Kitamura, Chief Yagami was the one who charged into the station.
北村次長、突っ込んだのは夜神局長でした
How are your preparations proceeding?
そちらの準備は？
言われた通りにした
We've done as you asked.
夜神さん、五分後に正面玄関から堂々と出てきてください
Yagami-san, please leave openly through the front entrance in five minutes.
Openly? Through the front entrance?
正面から堂々と…？
There are to be no gaps! Understood?!
いいか、隙間を作るな
Ensure that you aren't seen!
自分達の姿は見せるな
キラはテレビ局内には居ない！居るなら外だ！
Kira won't be inside the station; if they're here, they're outside!
Thank you.
ありがとう…
I'll drive myself.
自分で運転する
わかりました
Understood.
Listen up!
いいか、ここから見える範囲にキラがいる可能性は十分にある
There's a good chance that Kira may be somewhere within visual range.
Devise methods of searching that ensures you can't be seen.
こちらの姿を見られぬ様、工夫し捜索しろ
警察は、キラの呼びかけには応じず、戦う姿勢を見せました
The police have ignored Kira, and have shown us that they are ready to fight.
I-It takes courage for me to say this... but what they are doing is right! This is right!
わ…私はあえて勇気を出して言います
これで正しい、これで正しいと
I-It takes courage for me to say this... but what they are doing is right! This is right!
This is the position a constitutional nation should take!
これが法治国家の取るべき、正しい姿勢です
My name is Tanakabara Kouki.
私の名前は田中原高樹、
The announcer for NHN's "Golden news"... Tanakabara Kouki!
NHN ゴールデンニュースアナウンサーの田中原高樹であります
Chief!
局長！
Chief Yagami!
夜神局長！
Ryuuzaki... I apologize for acting on impulse.
竜崎、勝手な真似をしてすまなかった…
It seems I got a little too emotional.
感情的になりすぎたようだ
Not at all.
いえ
これに、キラが送ってきた
All the envelopes and tapes sent by Kira are in here.
封筒、テープ全部入っている
Thank you very much.
ありがとうございます
L-Let me rest for a while...
す…少し休ませてくれ…
Yagami-san, I won't let this go to waste.
夜神さん、
無駄にはしません
It's postmarked from Osaka.
消印は大阪か…
However, Kira is able to manipulate people before death, so they wouldn't have to go to Osaka themselves to mail this.
しかしキラは死の前の行動を操れる
自分で大阪まで行き投函しなくても出せる…
Aizawa-san, can I ask you to analyze these?
相沢さん、
これの鑑識お願いできますか？
鑑識には顔がきく、徹底的に調べさせます
I'm good at that. I'll do a thorough job.
Please do.
お願いします
私は、コピーテープの方で内容を確認します
I'll confirm the contents of the copied tapes.
How is it, Ryuuzaki?
どうだ、竜崎
It was an interesting video.
面白いビデオでした
If the police agree to cooperate with Kira, there are orders to broadcast video three, and if they refuse, video four is to be played.
警察がキラの協力に YES と答えたら…
三のビデオを放映指示してあり、 NO なら四を放映です
If the police agree to cooperate with Kira, there are orders to broadcast video three, and if they refuse, video four is to be played.
On video three, there are detailed conditions regarding the cooperation.
三には協力の細かい条件、
In a nutshell, it's to report information on more criminals.
簡単に言うと、犯罪者をより多く報道すること
Even if they've committed less serious crimes, there are instructions to pick out those who harm others, and those that abuse the weak and vulnerable.
特に軽犯罪でも人を傷つけた者、
弱い者への虐待はできる限り取り上げろと言う事です
Even if they've committed less serious crimes, there are instructions to pick out those who harm others, and those that abuse the weak and vulnerable.
Kira will then decide whether to pass judgement on them or not.
そして裁くかどうか決めるのはキラ
In addition, as proof that the police are willing to cooperate, they order both L and a senior member of the police to appear on TV,
それと、警察が協力することの証として、
「警察幹部と L がテレビに出演し、
キラに協力すると発表しろ」と言っています
and announce "We will cooperate with Kira".
幹部と共に私の顔を晒させ、警察に妙な動きが出たら、
By exposing the faces of myself and a senior policeman, should the police attempt anything funny, they would be able to kill us.
そこから殺していくというわけです
What about the contents of the fourth video, if we answer "no"?
それで… NO と答えた場合の四のビデオの内容は…
It's more or less the same thing, but said in a different way.
言い方が違うだけで、殆ど同じです
The answer is bound to be "no", Yagami-san. Please authorize Sakura TV to play tape four.
夜神さん、返事は当然 NO でしょうし、
四のビデオをさくらテレビに放映することを、
許可してあげてください
The answer is bound to be "no", Yagami-san. Please authorize Sakura TV to play tape four.
I think that it's a great shame that you've chosen to answer "no".
答えは NO という事を、大変残念に思います
Since this reply indicates that the police will persistently fight against me,
警察はあくまで私と戦うと言う返事ですから、
I will have to take the life of the Chief of the Japanese Police Force, or alternatively, the life of the person directing this investigation, known as L.
まず、日本警察庁長官の命、
もしくは、捜査の指揮を執っているとされる、
I will have to take the life of the Chief of the Japanese Police Force, or alternatively, the life of the person directing this investigation, known as L.
L なる人物の命を取ります
The Chief of Police or L?
長官か L か、平和な世界への協力をしなかった犠牲として、
Which one of you will pay the price for deciding not to help me create a peaceful world?
どちらを差し出すか
Please decide within four days.
四日間で決めてください
やはり神は僕の味方をしている…
God is on my side after all.
Well, when I say "God", I mean "Shinigami".
神と言っても今回は、死神だけどね
へぇ、みたいだな
Looks that way.
Another Shinigami has come down to Earth, and that Shinigami's Death Note has passed into the hands of a human who supports Kira.
人間界にもう一匹の死神が舞い降りた…
そしてその死神のデスノートは、キラに賛同する人間の手にある
It's highly probable that this Kira has the eyes of a Shinigami.
おそらくコイツは死神の目を持っている…
つまり殺傷能力は…遥かに僕より優るキラ
In other words, this Kira's ability to kill is far greater than mine.
Given the current situation, it'll be fine to leave them alone for a while.
今の状況なら放っておいてもよかろう、
L が葬られる可能性もある
There's a good chance that L will be buried.
But, what I can't forgive, is that they've lowered Kira's dignity by using such inferior methods!
しかし…こんな卑劣なやり方で、
キラの品位を落としたのは、許せることでもない
But, what I can't forgive, is that they've lowered Kira's dignity by using such inferior methods!
It'll also be problematic if the fake messes up, gets caught, and people find out about the Death Note.
偽がヘマをして捕まり、デスノートの存在を知られてもまずい
あまり長く野放しにしてばおけない…
I can't leave them to their own devices for too long.
今、僕が一番理想とするのは、
Right now, the ideal thing for me to do would be... to help out with the investigation, and grasp both L's and the fake Kira's moves.
捜査本部に協力し、
L の動きと偽キラの動きを…把握すること
Right now, the ideal thing for me to do would be... to help out with the investigation, and grasp both L's and the fake Kira's moves.
Ryuuzaki, it's just as we thought.
竜崎、思っていた通りだ
Of their own accord, world leaders have discussed this, and they want the real L to appear on TV.
各国首脳が勝手に話し合い、
本物の L をテレビに出演させろと言ってきた…
Of their own accord, world leaders have discussed this, and they want the real L to appear on TV.
That is the correct choice to make, but we still have three days, so let's try and think of some countermeasures.
それが一番正しい選択です
まぁ、まだ三日ありますから、対策を考えましょう
That is the correct choice to make, but we still have three days, so let's try and think of some countermeasures.
I'd be pretty upset... if I was killed by someone who's merely jumping onto the "Kira" bandwagon.
私も不愉快ですから…
キラに便乗した者に殺されるのは
I'd be pretty upset... if I was killed by someone who's merely jumping onto the "Kira" bandwagon.
What do you mean by that, Ryuuzaki?!
どういう意味だ、竜崎
The probability of this Kira being a fake is extremely high.
このキラはキラの偽者の可能性が高い、
No, a "second Kira" is probably a better description.
いや、第二のキラと言うべきでしょう
A second Kira?
第二のキラ!?
な…何故第二のキラがいると思うのか
What makes you think that there's a second Kira?
ちゃんと話してくれないか
Please explain this to us.
まず、自分がキラだとテレビ局員に信じさせる為に、
ビデオで予告殺人した犠牲者について
Firstly, if you look at the first tape used to convince the TV station's employees,
it's noticeable that the victims of the predicted deaths, were only reported on the "Wide Show" or in women's magazines.
このふたりの事件は、
女性週刊誌とワイドショーでしか報道されていなかった
it's noticeable that the victims of the predicted deaths, were only reported on the "Wide Show" or in women's magazines.
The real Kira wouldn't have bothered with such small fry.
本物のキラなら、そんな雑魚でやってみせる必要はない
But, if we think of them as a second Kira... it'd have been too risky for them to use any criminal that the real Kira may potentially kill before them.
しかし第二のキラにしてみれば…
本物のキラが殺す可能性のある犯罪者を予告には使えなかった
But, if we think of them as a second Kira... it'd have been too risky for them to use any criminal that the real Kira may potentially kill before them.
竜崎、第二のキラと言う可能性は一体、どのくらい…
Ryuuzaki, what are the chances of there being a second Kira?
This time it's over 70%.
今回は七十パーセント以上です
大体やり方が気に入らない、キラらしくない
Either way, I don't like their methods... It's unlike Kira.
らしくない？
"Unlike"?
今までキラは、
追う者は別として、罪の無い者の犠牲は避けていた
Up till now, with the exception of those chasing after them, Kira has avoided sacrificing the innocent.
片方のキラが捕まれば、
もう片方を捕まえるヒントを少なからず生れると思うんです
If we can catch one of the Kiras, I think that we'll get hints to help catch the other.
Yagami-san, would it be okay if we asked your son to help us in the investigation?
夜神さん、息子さんに捜査協力を願っても宜しいでしょうか
So, am I to understand that you no longer suspect him?
それは…息子の疑いは完全に晴れたと受け取っていいのか？
いえ、疑いは晴れたとは言えませんが、
息子さんの推理力は期待できる
No, I can't say that I don't still suspect him, but I am counting on his skills of deduction.
So that's what you mean...
そういう意味か…
If this is what my son wants, I see no reason to stop him.
息子が協力するといえば、止める理由は無い
Thank you very much.
ありがとうございます、ただし…
But, please don't tell him that we suspect that this Kira may be a fake.
今回のキラが偽者かもしれないという事は、
伏せておいて下さい
Please give the impression that we're determinedly pursuing one Kira.
あくまでもキラを追っているという形でお願いします
Hey, Misa... I kindly gave that Death Note to you, so why don't you use it more for yourself?
なぁ、ミサ
せっかくデスノートをあげたのに、
Hey, Misa... I kindly gave that Death Note to you, so why don't you use it more for yourself?
もっと自分の為に利用しなくていいのか？
自分の為に使ってるよ、
I am using it for myself.
After all, I support Kira!
だってキラに賛成だし
So I want to know what kind of person Kira is.
キラがどんな人か知りたいの
会ってお話したいとも思ってるよ
And I want to meet and talk to them.
That's why I went through the trouble of sending those tapes to the TV station, and ensured that I could get Kira to notice me!
その為にわざわざ、テレビにあんなの送って、
キラに気づいてもらえるようにしたんだから
キラは興味持ってくれたよね、きっと
Kira will be interested. I'm sure of it!
That's a dangerous game you're playing.
危ない遊びだね、
You could be killed. You know that, right?
殺されるかもしれない。わかってる？
It'll be okay. I'm sure Kira is kind to innocent girls.
大丈夫だよ、キラはきっと純粋な子には優しいし、
And if it does come to that...
いざとなったら、
Misa is stronger because she has the eyes!
目を持ってる海砂の方が…強いもん！
To be continued
なん
何にしても偽キラの事は、
本部の人間より、一歩先を知る必要がある
それにしても、一体どんな奴なんだ…
偽キラ